# MANYU LAKHOTIA

+1(337)322-4192 ♦ LakeMonYew@gmail.com ♦ https://portfolio.majorziploc.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/majorziploc/ \$\displayhttps://github.com/MajorZiploc \$\displayhttps://majorziploc.itch.io/

Software Developer with 6+ years of work experience in developing web applications, stand alone applications, cicd, and databases; along with personal experience in art/design, scripting, web scraping, gamedev, data analytics, and data cleaning.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend react, redux, jquery, css, sass, html, material ui, bootstrap, krita, inkscape, winforms, cypress.io

Backend/Testing/Headless django, express, nodejs, asp.net mvc, google app suite, jest, pandas, webscraper.io, tampermonkey

Languages javascript, python, typescript, bash, sql, mongodb, php, redis, java, C#, F#, powershell, rbql, vimscript

DevOps docker, aws, kubernetes, gitlab ci, github actions, ansible, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity, vmware

### EXPERIENCE

## Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8 Optimal Dynamics

(Logistics)

Feb 2024 - Present New York, NY

• Utilized tools like: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

## Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8

May 2022 - Jan 2024 Minneapolis, MN

Conservis (Agriculture)

- Improved authentication by moving from homebrewed auth solution to keycloak
- Use krita and inkscape to design frontend mockups and create svg icons
- Utilized tools like: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

## Software Developer - Full time - Mostly Remote - Team size: 4-10

Mar 2020 - Apr 2022

Acadian Ambulance

(Medical)

Lafayette, LA

- Led development of an ambulance scheduling system
- Introduced automated UI and API testing using Cypress.io
- Utilized tools like: F#, C#, react, redux, wsl, mssql, docker, just, bash, microservices, aws, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity

#### Software Developer - Part time - Remote - Team size: 3-5 Cythereal (Cyber security)

Created dashboard to investigate potential malware samples

Jun 2021 - Apr 2022

Lafayette, LA

• Utilized tools like: django, react, redux, docker, mongodb, redis, rpm, bash, azure, ansible, terraform, packer, just

#### Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 10-15 CGI (Medical)

• Migrated legacy health insurance portal to more modern solutions

Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Lafayette, LA

- Utilized tools like: django, react, redux, docker, redis, mongodb, bash, openshift, vscode

## Research Assistant - Part time - Hybrid

University Of Louisiana

(Programming Languages)

May 2018 - Dec 2018

Lafayette, LA

Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 4-6

Wetlands Research Center

(Aquaculture)

Dec 2016 - Dec 2018 Lafayette, LA

• Developed a stand alone java swing app for analyzing geospatial water levels from large NetCDF files

## OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

F# projects with contributions FSharpPlus, Acadian.FSharp, Acadian.Dapper.Fs, Acadian.Json.Fs (Available on nuget)

keycloak A oauth2 library with user federations, management and more (Available on maven) (java)

nvim-dev-container A nvim plugin for remote devcontainers using same configs as vscode devcontainers (lua)

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelors in Economics with Computer Science and Mathematics, University of Louisiana at Lafayette

2016 - 2018

Associates in General Studies Business, South Louisiana Community College

2013 - 2015